Hi. In this course, you're going to learn how to develop servers using FastAPI.
And FastAPI is fast in two ways.
One, it's fast in development.
So from zero to have something that works, it's really fast and also
not a lot of code.
It's also fast in performance.
It can efficiently serve a lot of requests.
FastAPI has established itself as one of the web servers in the Python ecosystem.
It's widely adopted.
There's great documentation, there's a lot of ecosystem around it,
and it's also fun to use.
Hi, I'm Miki Tebeka, and I've been writing web servers for 20-something years now.
So join me and see why you should use FastAPI as the web server
for your next project.